# T.C. Rotunda

tcrotunda@gmail.com | (714) 883-7973

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tcrotunda/ | GitHub: https://github.com/tcrotunda | Website: https://tcrotunda.github.io/

#### Summary

Data Specialist with 6+ years of experience working as a Business Analyst and Data Analyst for top financial firms such as JP Morgan, BNY Mellon, and Charles Schwab. Self-starter, fast learning, and can retain information at a high level. Motivated to learn new technologies. Have a passion for data, and excel in team-oriented environments. Highly detail-oriented, and able to juggle multiple projects at a time. Excellent written and verbal communication skills. Certificate in Data Analytics and Visualization through University of California, Berkeley.

## **Technical Skills**

Python, SQL, Tableau, JavaScript, R, HTML, CSS, AWS, VBA, API, MongoDB, Postgres, Hadoop, Jira, Confluence, SAP Business Objects, GitHub, GitLab, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint

# **Employment**

Charles Schwab (Apex Systems)

San Francisco, CA

May2020 - Present

**Business Analyst** 

- Work with developers to build a new font-end UI to display trade orders for portfolio managers due to a change in vendor
- Query databases using SQL to check data while conducting UAT and QA testing, and question / improve functionality and
  efficiencies
- Lead daily project scrum calls to ensure timely competition of user stories and appropriate allocation of resources
- Work as a team to test vendor account and trade management system
- Work with developers to migrate ETF trade order processing file from former vendor to new vendor
- Create production support documentation for import and export feeds for Aladdin trading system
- Fill in gaps on various teams and projects when needed

#### JPMorgan Chase & Co.

New York, NY

Associate Business Data Analyst

February 2019 - June 2019

Business Data Analyst

February 2016 - January 2019

- Analyzed and managed primary and secondary sourced data for the US Funds Management Data Warehouse (FMDW), specifically
  minimizing data errors for the Finance Team for financial reporting purposes
- Led and assisted with projects to maintain data feeds of sourced data for FMDW, and to streamline, automate and improve new
  downstream data feeds to other business units
- Communicated and coordinated with various lines of business, and serve as a liaison between business and technology to help improve business processes and drive changes to our ETL
- Used SAP Business Objects to query data for analysis, reporting (daily, monthly, quarterly), UAT testing, and data quality purposes
- Maintained SAP Business Objects infrastructure and data model/data mapping for FMDW
- Worked with international teams from Europe and Asia
- Helped train new and junior team members

Boston, MA

Associate Business Analyst

June 2014 - January 2016

- Assisted to manage and mitigate risk by maintaining data and data flow for multiple systems for the Wealth Management Fixed Income trading desk through reconciliation reporting
- Updated and adjusted SQL queries to find specific data for ad hoc or future needs
- Worked directly with vendor for application updates and new features to meet end user needs
- Served as a liaison between Portfolio Managers (users) and the technology group
- Helped manage and mitigate risk within the business unit

EverFi Inc.

Newton, MA
Services and Curriculum Intern

June 2013 – May 2014

Performed Level-2 Technical Support and testing for technology-based education system

### Education

### University of California, Berkeley

Berkeley, CA

Certificate in Data Analytics and Visualization

January 2021

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in Excel, VBA, Python, R, JavaScript, SQL Databases, Tableau, Big Data, and Machine Learning

#### Suffolk University Sawyer Business School

Boston, MA

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration Management, Information Systems minor Awards: Magna Cum Laude | GPA: 3.77 May 2014